"The Everyday Tale of Every Ashen Witch"
Let me tell you about myself.
I am a witch and a traveler.
My journey was a series
of meetings and farewells,
and at the same time,
it was a series of choices.
I made many choices
that I couldn't backtrack on,
and that has brought me to where I am today.
"The Country That Makes Your Wishes Come True"?
I want to be super rich. I want to be
super rich. I want to be super rich--
This is...
What is the meaning of this?
This is not what I wished for...
That's Mirarosé's...
Please don't move!
Are you a safe me? Or an evil me?
What do you mean "an evil me"?
Why are there two of me, anyway?
How much did those glasses cost?
Um, who are you?
The Ashen Witch, Elaina.
I'm the Ashen Witch, Elaina, too...
Yeah, it looks like it.
It wasn't my wish to meet another me, though...
It wasn't ours, either.
"Ours"? How many me's are there?
I don't know how many there are
in total, but there are 15 of us here.
Fifteen?!
--Tee-hee!
--Oh, how nice.
--Oh... I want to die...
--Tee-hee!
--Oh, how nice.
--Oh... I want to die...
--I can guess where everyone's
hidden their money...
--It's not like there's any hope.
--I can guess where everyone's
hidden their money...
Everyone, be quiet.
Let me introduce you. This is the 16th me.
Um, hello.
Oh! You're cosplaying me, too!
I don't really get doing it
without permission, though!
I'm gonna charge you a usage fee.
Ten billion gold coins!
She gets excited about money,
so she's not the "Ash" Witch,
she's Excited Me, the "Cash" Witch, Elaina.
The Cash Witch...
Whoo! Nice to meet ya!
The one over there is the dumb me.
Hi, me number 16!
Oh, no one's there.
Nice to meet you. Tee-hee!
Whoa!
Ouch! Tee-hee!
She seems less dumb and more like a klutz...
This is the me who loves girls.
Sixteen whole me's.
Oh, so many of me...
Am I in heaven?
Less like she likes girls,
and more like she likes herself...
This one has a strange complex
about the size of her breasts.
Oh? You're supposed to be the same as me,
but for some reason, your chest
looks deflated compared to mine.
What's the matter?
Have you been drinking your milk?
Please wait! My chest--
So pointless...
That me is kind of moody.
--Oh, my chest...
--What're you looking at, bastard?
You wanna fight? Wanna fight? Huh?
Next to her is the greedy me.
If I take the money from all the
me's here, then I'll be super rich...
Sounds like the usual me...
This is the cringey me.
The black dragon thing imprisoned
in my eye is trying to attack all of you--
Get away from me!
This is the love-struck maiden me.
Saya...
Saya, Saya...
Why Saya?
The one hiding over there is me
with a deep darkness in my heart.
I want to die.
What happened?
And there's me with a deep
darkness in my heart, number two.
I hate this... The outside is scary...
Why are you traveling then?
And me with a deep darkness
in my heart, number three.
I can't take it anymore...
All the me's here should just die...
I have too many deep darknesses.
Over there is the me with a foreign affectation.
--Khorosho.
--Is this a show?
This is the gelatinous me.
That's not even human anymore.
This is the me that turned into a ghoul.
Why?
And I am the intellectual me.
You think highly of yourself, huh?
It's the truth. And--
I'd like to call you something, too.
Everyone, any ideas?
What traits does the sixteenth me have?
--None! Tee-hee.
--My cosplay! One hundred billion gold coins!
--She's got no personality.
--No personality and no boobs.
--No eyepatch or bandages...
--No money.
--Oh, 16 me's...
--Wherefore art thou Saya...?
--I want to die...
--Me, too...
--Rest in peace...
--I want to die...
--Khorosho.
I see, I see. Thank you very much.
That was a big help.
What kind of help could that have been...?
And so, I'd like to call you "Protagonist Me."
What do you think?
What train of thought led you
to that incomprehensible name?
I tried turning your weakness of
having no personality into a strength.
I'm not happy to be told
I have no personality, though.
Don't worry about it, No Personality.
It means you can become anything, you know?
It's perfect for a protagonist, No Personality.
So, why are we all holed up in this place?
In this country, there's one
evil me mixed in with the rest.
She's violent and attacks
every time she meets another me.
Oh?
She's a violent me, so we call her Violent Me.
Just like her description, huh?
So you're holed up here to
run away from that violent me?
But Violent Me is also me, isn't she?
If you fought normally,
you'd at least get a draw, right?
Protagonist Me, please think about it carefully.
If the opponent is also me,
then that means I'd have to hurt myself.
Can you imagine what would happen if she died?
Hmm... I can't.
We can't either!
Since we don't know, there's nothing we can do,
so that's why we're gathered
here to talk about it. Hah!
And so, what do you think we should do?
I don't know what to do, either...
What are you saying?
You're Protagonist Me, right?
At a time like this, we need
the protagonist to take the helm.
By the way, my role is that of an
adviser who assists the protagonist.
So, you led everyone to call me
Protagonist Me so you could use me?
What a schemer. As expected of me.
If that's how you feel, then...
Now, all the me's other than me
should go investigate the town.
I'll stay here and wait for
all the me's to come back.
What're you saying, you little--
--The protagonist should step down! Step down!
--Oh, I'm so dignified...
--Is your brain smaller than a flea?
--You're lower than boobs!
--How much will you give me?
--Is your brain smaller than a flea?
--You're lower than boobs!
--My right hand is about to go wild.
--Saya...
--I want to go to heaven...
--I want to go... back inside my mother...
--Saya...
--I want to go to heaven...
--I want to go... back inside my mother...
--The messenger of hell isn't coming for me...
--You said it!
What? You're the ones who put me
up on a pedestal as the protagonist.
Jeez, I'm so selfish. In that case, tell me--
Oh, no! Ghoul Me died!
It's really grotesque!
It was definitely an instant death.
Gel Me has also been crushed
and is in a gelatinous state!
Oh, they're alive. Damn it...
I'm glad they're okay...
You people were gathered here, huh?
This is perfect.
Don't tell me that me is...
Yes, Violent Me.
I will dispose of every single last me.
Is the me sitting on the throne over
there the leader of all the me's here?
I don't know if I'm the leader or not,
but I'm called Protagonist Me.
I see, I see. Is that right?
You're the protagonist?
Please die!
I don't know why in the world you're
so upset that you would attack me,
but are you saying you can beat 16 me's?
Oh, Gel Me and Ghoul Me
are down, so there are 14.
Are you saying you can beat 14 me's?
I don't live in a carefree world
like the ones you all live in.
--Could it be that you've never
looked in a mirror before?
--Sneak... Sneak...
--Could it be that you've never
looked in a mirror before?
Even though you're also a me.
Take that!
Oh, my big boobs...!
Scary, scary, scary, scary...
I want to go home...
Please don't come closer!
Into the dark!
I'll go home now...
Into the darkness...
I-It was a trap?
It's like we're about to be executed...
I just want to return to the earth like this...
It's nice and cool and calming...
She's not here?
I-I made a mistake!
Not this money...!
Y-You bastard!
You're not going to fight?
I was watching.
And?
I thought that you're not
an opponent I can't beat.
How impertinent.
Yes, the same as you.
Why is your hair still short?
You know why my hair was cut off, don't you?
Yes. Because my hair was
also cut off in that country.
I didn't have the energy to
put my hair back to normal.
I couldn't save a single
person in that country...
Have you ever seen the instant love
turns to hate with your own eyes?
The instant when someone turns to a person
they just loved with murderous intent?
I haven't.
And? Was your hair cut by the Ripper after that?
Your journey was a very different one from mine.
Different...
Yes, different. Completely.
I'm different from you all, as I thought.
What about it?
You said you saw the moment love turns to hate.
With just that, did you lose
the energy to get your hair back,
and enter a state of despair?
I really didn't wish for
anything like this at all.
It wasn't despair. I seethed with anger.
Oh? At what?
Isn't it obvious?
At myself!
At the me's who kept
traveling carefree, unlike me,
and at myself, who couldn't do anything
even when faced with cruel reality!
She's really taking her anger out on us.
As expected of me.
You should...
You should just disappear!
Who are you saying that to?
To me? Or to yourself?
This country is supposed
to make wishes come true.
I can't forgive the me's who traveled
carefree without knowing any pain,
so I'm sure that's why I'm here!
To make the other me's experience
the same thing as me!
That's your wish, not ours.
Then, why are we all gathered here?
You don't know? Or are you
pretending not to know?
We threw our magic at each
other with everything we had,
but unfortunately, we were so evenly matched
that in the end, even after
we'd both used up all our magic,
nothing was settled.
Why in the world did I come to this country?
First, let me tell you what I was
kind of wishing deep inside my heart.
I came here to meet the other me's.
I was probably dying
to see the other possibilities.
"Other possibilities"...
Journeys are a series of meetings and farewells,
and at the same time,
they are a series of choices.
I might've had some other choices...
Possibilities other than me...
That's why I came here and
met the other versions of us.
But that doesn't explain why I'm here...
It does.
I'm sure you also felt a yearning
for the other me's, like I did.
A yearning for a me that wasn't
caught up in the middle of the sorrow
at the Clock Village of Rostolf
is what led you here.
You probably came here
wishing for a version of yourself that
hadn't experienced all that sorrow.
Not in order to hurt us,
but to heal yourself.
That's self-centered.
Did you say "self-centered"?
There's no one here but yourself.
Will you listen to my story?
About how I went back in
time ten years in that country.
That's what I came here for.
And so, I made peace with myself,
and we talked until dark.
When we went back to the castle,
we shared our diaries,
and took turns reading about all our travels.
Everyone, I've thought of something good.
Something good?
We wrote in our diaries in order
to tell Mom about our travels,
but do you want to turn
this into a book someday?
A book?
Yes. Like The Adventures of Niké--
No, a story about our travels that
will surpass The Adventures of Niké.
That's a great idea!
As expected of Protagonist Me.
I'm in! I'm in!
Nice idea!
A book about our dark past... Not bad.
Khorosho!
Meow!
What should we do about the title then?
"The Adventures of Elaina"!
Just like Niké, huh?
"Let's Go, Elaina!"
"Blooming Lily Elaina."
"You Can Have Big Boobs, Too!"
"How to Glare Properly."
"How to Make One Trillion Gold Coins."
"Elaina's Dream Diary."
"The Days of Saya and My Love."
"Elaina: Hell Part."
"Elaina: Stairway to Heaven."
"Happiest at Home."
"Khorosho!"
Um, will all the me's please
think about this seriously?
And so, after intense discussion,
the name of the book was finally decided.
Saya...
Oh, so cute...
Khorosho...
What do you plan on doing after this?
I think I'll try and get my hair back.
It's probably still on the doll.
Really?
Yes. Well, the culprit's
already been caught, though,
so I should be good once I find the doll.
Thanks, Elaina.
You're welcome, Elaina.
Good night.
Huh?
A dream?
"Wandering Witch"
Now, shall I go?
And now, a question for you.
Who's the witch flying
through the clear blue sky,
so beautiful that if someone were there,
they would definitely look back and sigh?
It's the person traveling and writing
my--our--story, Wandering Witch--
That's right. It's me!
"Wandering Witch"
I-I'm sorry! I was caught up in my writing--
No, I should've paid more attention, too.
But you should look at your
surroundings when you walk.
You're just making your
own field of vision smaller.
I'm sorry. Thank you.
Well, let's both be more careful next time.
R-Right.
"Wandering Witch"
"Read This When You Wake Up in the Morning"
I didn't know yet
that she and I would be
traveling together in the future.
Her name is Amnesia.